greenpolkadotbox.com 2019-02-02

# Organic and Non-GMO Foods, Shipped to Your Door

**Green PolkaDot Box (“GPDB”) and its Health Merchants, including this store,  **know you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy.  **By visiting this GPDB Health Merchant platform you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

 **Information You Give Us:**  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our store and communicating with you. We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

 **Automatic Information:**  
We use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our store or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of this website.

 **Information We Share:**  
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. In such cases, they may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

 **Protection of Green Polka Dot Box and Others:**  
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Green PolkaDot Box and our Health Merchants, including the owners of this store, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

 **Information Security:**  
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

 **Information You Can Access:**  
This store gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with Amazon.com for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.

 **Your Choices:**

  1. As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such store features as your Account Dashboard, Shopping Lists, On the Dot™ Subscriptions and Customer Reviews. You can add or update certain information on pages such as those referenced in the Account Dashboard section.

  2. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your preferences in your Account Dashboard. (If you do not want to receive promotions or other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of this Web store, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.)

  3. This store does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults for children.

 **Examples of Information Collected:**  
You provide us most information when you search, buy, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product; place an order through this store; provide information in your Account Dashboard (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when shopping with us) or communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; use our services such as My Shopping Lists, On the Dot™ subscriptions and your Promotion Bank; and provide and rate Reviews. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers; credit card information; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including addresses and phone number; e-mail addresses of your friends and other customers; content of reviews and e-mails to us; personal description and photograph in your Account information or profile; and financial information, including Social Security and driver's license numbers.

  1.  **Information You Give Us:**  
Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create features Top Sellers and Products that Work ; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and the phone number you used to call our 800 number. We may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of our Web site for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. We may also collect technical information to help us identify your device for fraud prevention and diagnostic purposes.

  2.  **Information from Other Sources:**  
Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily; account information, purchase or redemption information, and page-view information from some merchants with which we operate co-branded businesses or for which we provide technical, fulfillment, advertising, or other services; search term and search result information from some searches conducted through the Web search features offered by our subsidiary, Alexa Internet; search results and links, including paid listings (such as Sponsored Links); and credit history information from credit bureaus, which we use to help prevent and detect fraud and to offer certain credit or financial services to some customers.

  3.  **Information You Can Access:**  
Examples of information you can access easily at this store includes up-to-date information regarding recent orders; personally identifiable information (including name, e-mail, password, communications and personalized advertising preferences, address book, and check out settings); payment settings (including credit card information and promotional certificate and gift card balances); e-mail notification settings (including newsletters); Recommendations (including Recommended for You and Improve Your Recommendations); and shopping lists.
